so if you loved the 90s then you know about guy and it had the lead singer aaron hall and they
was singing don't be afraid which if you hear the lyrics you should be afraid and then you see this
headline and then i want you to watch this video and then i want us to have a real quick conversation
everybody know me yeah so everybody know if i say it i'm gonna fuck it to death i like the
fucking public you feel me yeah so niggas can't say nothing about it them square ass niggas them
precious cake little dick niggas yeah i like for them niggas to see how i fuck like if you speak to
joe to see your puffy or any of them niggas they've been at my house they all see me fuck they all know
i'm a big nigga yeah if a bitch touch my dick and she say my dick is small then she's a lying bitch
yeah tell her to name the tattoo that's on my ribs that says warning you get these niggas i'm fucking
you up the thing is a whole lot of niggas write about taking girls out to shop taking girls
to fly to dubai and all that shit bitch close your eyes we anywhere you feel me and my whole
thing is this my whole thing is this is that if you can handle my dick and you can make me still
be aaron hall without fucking rapping off your mouth then i'll take you anywhere other than that
shit you back home bitch aside from him just demonstrating that he is a terrible misogynist
chauvinistic and abusive man his obsession with his penis is bewildering i want to break this to y'all
out there who are really standing on i got a big old dick a lot of dicks are big i know they say like
the average is this size it's not that hard to run into a big old dick it it really isn't and for
the record even the possession of a big old dick don't mean shit you didn't do anything to get it
except be born with it even women we have to do kegels to increase the intensity of our tightness y'all
don't do nothing there ain't no dick push-ups to do there ain't no dick squats to do you just got
lucky okay you just got lucky that's it i'd also like to add just because you got a big old thing
don't mean you're doing big things with it or without also who is the brother that was in the
back that was just hype hype hype hype hype hype like is that big old they paying your bills if that
wasn't his daddy saying that's my dick then there was no need for all of that he was spliff star in this
man's penis